

# **Profile**

Professional C# .Net software developer with experience of over 9 years in Commercial/Enterprise level software development. I have experience in client interaction roles, in which efficiency and quality of work was detrimental to project growth. Looking for opportunities with challenging roles and exciting domains.

# **Employment History**

#### Software Developer, Nagarro Software, Vienna

MARCH 2014 - PRESENT

C# .Net Consultant with a leading Austrian bank, one of the largest financial service provider in central and eastern Europe. Working on Winforms application, .Net Core Web API, WCF services. Creating and maintaining applications for supporting banking operations,

#### Tools & Technology:

c#, .net 4.7, .net core 2.1, WCF, WEB API, Winforms, Entity Framework, SQL Server, MS Build, Jenkins, Bit Bucket, TFS, IIS, REST, SOAP, Microservices

#### Roles & Responsibilities:

- Currently involved in 3 projects in the capacity of c# developer (Leasing Domain)
- Designing & developing new features
- Code review and unit testing
- Build and deployment activities
- Interacting with the customers/Users
- Providing support for Operational & Production issues
- Maintaining Dev, QA & Prod environments
- Process automation & improvements to reduce operational overheads
- Setting up application servers
- Requirement gathering, Estimations, Sprint planning
- Application packaging and Delivery

#### Software Developer, Aon Hewitt, Gurgaon, India

JUNE 2010 - MARCH 2014

C# .Net developer at Aon Hewitt (originally Hewitt Associates), one of the top HR Consulting firm in the US. Creating and maintaining existing applications for supporting the HR consulting business .

#### Tools & Technology:

Visual Studio 2010, c# , .net 2.0 , Web Services, .Net Remoting and IBM DB2 V9.5, MS Build, VSS, SVN

#### Roles & Responsibilities:

- Involved in development and maintenance of Windows Application for supporting HR & Consulting delivery teams.
- Creating Low level Design documents, designing modules and peer reviews
- POCs and analysing requirements from onsite counterparts
- Providing offshore production support
- Analysing and resolving operational issues

## **Details**

+4368864020316 vivek.mishra04@yahoo.com

NATIONALITY

Indian

11 Dec 1986

### Skills

C#

**SQL** 

Winforms

HTML/CSS

WCF

Web API

**Entity Framework** 

**ASP.NET MVC** 

Angular

# Languages

English

German

French

# Education

Masters in Computer Applications, Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, New Delhi

2007 - 2010

B.Sc Computer Science, University of Delhi, New Delhi

2004 - 2007